<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- EN: poluxkin -->
  <VRE_Poluxkin.label>поллу-фітон</VRE_Poluxkin.label>

  <!-- EN: Based on genetic data retrofitted from Gauranlen Inc.’s investment into dendrology following the Fall of Sorne, phytokins are plant-based humanoids with an emphasis on symmetry and symbiosis. Their ability to subsist only on sunlight and affinity with any and all plantlife make them especially suited to aiding newly established colonies or underperforming industrial farms.\n\nBased on research from the forest planet of Phytok that committed to extensive analysis on human-compatibility with psychic energy, phytokin xenogerms are typically exclusive to high-ranking, supporting roles in megacorporations and planetary governments. Their unique way of reproduction has resulted in many identical offspring, with each generation becoming successively more competent than their progenitor, further contributing to their extremely low numbers. Their affinity with plantlife, along with the side effect of extremely high and ever-increasing psychic sensitivity, mean that any phytokin xenohumans found on the Rim are always adapted to high-concept, dominant trees that are present on their residing planet.\n\nThis particular xenogerm has adapted itself to Polux trees, allowing it to germinate new Polux bushes and improve local Polux bushes’ ability to consume toxic waste. While they are also immune to toxicity, they have developed a psychological requirement to consume and metabolize toxic wastepacks regularly. -->
  <VRE_Poluxkin.description>Фітони - це гуманоїди, створені на основі рослин з акцентом на симетрію та симбіоз. Спорідненість із рослинами та здатність харчуватися сонячним світлом робить їх дуже корисними для надання допомоги новим поселенням та недостатньо успішним фермерським господарствам на індустріальних світах.\n\nКсенотип був створений на основі досліджень, що проводяться на покритій лісами планеті Фіток, та присвячених аналізу сумісності людини з псі-енергією. Проте отримав він свій розвиток рахунок інвестицій корпорації «Гауранлен» після Падіння Сорна. Ксеносемена фітонів, як правило, призначені виключно для високопоставлених допоміжних посад у мегакорпораціях та планетарних адміністраціях.\n\nУнікальний спосіб розмноження фітонів призводить до появи безлічі ідентичних нащадків, причому кожне наступне покоління стає компетентнішим за попереднє. Це дозволяє компенсувати їхню надзвичайно низьку чисельність. Природна близькість до рослин, разом з побічним ефектом у вигляді надзвичайно високої та постійно зростаючої псі-чутливості, означає, що фітони, виявлені на околицях, гарантовано будуть психічно адаптовані до місцевих дерев.\n\nЦей ксенотип адаптований до дерев Поллукса, дозволяючи представникам ксенотипу вирощувати нові кущі Поллукса і посилювати їхню здатність поглинати токсичні відходи. Представники ксенотипу не тільки несприйнятливі до токсинів, а й виробили психологічну потребу в регулярному поглинанні та перетравленні відходів.</VRE_Poluxkin.description>

  <!-- EN: Powerful advisors to rulers and despots, poluxkins are beautiful and cunning and possess an ability to connect with a polux tree, greatly enhancing its abilities. They are immune to toxicity and in fact can help the environment by consuming and metabolizing waste. They are excellent at taking care of plants and reproduce via planting a saplingchild. -->
  <VRE_Poluxkin.descriptionShort>Впливові радники правителів та деспотів, фітони очищення красиві та хитромудрі. Вони мають здатність з'єднуватися з деревом Поллукса, значно посилюючи його можливості. Фітони очищення мають імунітет до отруєння токсинами та допомагають відновити чистоту навколишнього середовища, поглинаючи та переробляючи відходи. Цей ксенотип чудово підходить для догляду за рослинами і може відтворюватися шляхом посадки саджанців-нащадків.</VRE_Poluxkin.descriptionShort>
</LanguageData>
